Guide to the National Education Association-Commissions records, 1918-1982 NEA1002.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Commission on Professional Rights and Responsibilities, 1922-1981; Series 2; 82.75 Linear Feet
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Documents [file 1/2], 1963; Series 2 (Box 981, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Documents [file 2/2], 1963; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Don Wollott, 1964; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-General Correspondence, 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Interim and Progress Report Drafts, 1963; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-"Intolerable Conditions", 1963; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Material for Inquiry Team, 1963; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Newspaper Clippings [file 1/2], 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Newspaper Clippings [file 2/2], 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 982, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Persons Meeting with the Special Committee, 1963; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Press Releases, 1963; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-RBK, 1963; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-"Report by the Utah School Study Committee", February 1964; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Reports and Comments, 1963; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Special Committee, 1963; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-State Education Agency of Utah-Aftermath, 1950-1953; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Utah-Statewide-Utah State Education-Abridgement, 1950-1961; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Vermont-Springfield, 1971; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Charlottesville #218, 1966; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Colonial Heights #219 [file 1/2], 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Colonial Heights #219 [file 2/2], 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Colonial Heights-Press Clippings, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Hampton #215, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 983, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Norfolk, 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Northern Virginia Community College, 1969; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Radford, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Virginia Teachers Association #170, 1965; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Virginia-Wythe County #185, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Washington-Kelso-Abridgement, 1950-1964; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Washington-Kelso-Aftermath, 1950; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Washington-Port Angeles #305, 1968-1969; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Washington-Richland, 1964; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Washington-Seattle, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide #322 [file 1/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 984, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide #322 [file 2/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Background [file 1/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Background [file 2/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Committee, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Correspondence-WEA, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Exhibits, 1963-1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Financing [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 985, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Financing [file 2/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Investigation, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Newspaper Clippings, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Press, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Press Releases, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Reading the Report, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Report, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Request and Reports, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Requests for Investigation, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Rough Draft, 1971; Series 2 (Box 986, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Rough Draft II, 1974; Series 2 (Box 987, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Transcripts, April 21, 1971; Series 2 (Box 987, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Transcripts, April 21, 1971; Series 2 (Box 987, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Washington-Statewide-Transcripts, April 22, 1971; Series 2 (Box 987, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Jackson County #279 [file 1/3], 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Jackson County #279 [file 2/3], 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Jackson County #279 [file 3/3], 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Martinsburg #227, 1966; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Randolph County #295 [file 1/4], 1968; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Randolph County #295 [file 2/4], 1968; Series 2 (Box 988, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Randolph County #295 [file 3/4], 1968; Series 2 (Box 989, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-West Virginia-Randolph County #295 [file 4/4], 1968; Series 2 (Box 989, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha #196, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 989, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha [file 1/4], 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 989, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha [file 2/4], 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha [file 3/4], 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha [file 4/4], 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha-Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha-Preliminary Inquiry, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Kenosha-Special Committee, 1966-1968; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 6)
    Contains a "Diamond Disc" plastic record.
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-LaCrosse, 1971; Series 2 (Box 990, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Madison #152, 1965-1971; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Menasha #127, 1964; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee [file 1/3], 1966-1972; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee [file 2/3], 1966-1972; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee [file 3/3], 1966-1972; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Approval Slips, 1968; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Documents [file 1/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 991, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Documents [file 2/2], 1967; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Interim Report, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-News Clippings, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Report (Original), 1972; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Milwaukee-Special Committee, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin-Statewide-Requests for Investigation, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 6)
  - Joint Conference on Guidelines for Professional Practice Regulations, 1961; series 2 (Box 4290, Folder 19)
  - The Local Education Association and Grievance Adjustment, 1966; series 2 (Box 4290, Folder 20)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr.- Man and Teacher, 1968; Series 2 (Box 4627, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1964; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1965; Series 2 (Box 992, Folder 8)
  - Minutes [file 1/2], 1966; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 1)
  - Minutes [file 2/2], 1966; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1967; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1968; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1969; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1970; Series 2 (Box 993, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1971; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 1)
  - NEA Professional Rights and Responsibilities Committee on Civil and Human Rights of Educators Faculty Desegregation, 1966; series 2 (Box 4203, Folder 2)
  - New Mexico School Finance Study, October 1967; series 2 (Box 4290, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlets, 1962-1964; series 2 (Box 4383, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Issues, 1965; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 2)
  - A Plan for a New Type of Professional Training for a New Type of Teaching Staff, February 1968; series 2 (Box 4312, Folder 6)
  - Professional Rights and Responsibilities Handbook, 1963; series 2 (Box 4312, Folder 7)
  - Professional Rights and Repsonsibilities and the Local Education Association, December 1970; series 2 (Box 4400, Folder 1)
  - Professional Rights and Responsibilities and the Local Educational Association: A Developmental Paper Concerning Professional Rights and Responsibilities Purpose, Function, and Structure, March 1969; series 2 (Box 4290, Folder 22)
  - Project-Bill of Teachers Rights, 1964-1972; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"Belleville, New Jersey, A Study of Professional Responsibility when a Superintendent has Tenure of Office", January 1966; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 4)
  - Reports-"Bethpage Revisited (New York)", April 1963; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"Beyond Desegregation: the Problem of Power", February 1970; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 6)
    Included "Investigations, 1944-1967" (volumes 1-10).
  - Reports-"Brief of the National Education Association of the United States and the National Science Teachers Association as Amici Curiae" (Supreme Court, No. 749), October 1967; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"Central Issues Influencing School-Community Relations in Atlanta, Georgia", August 1969; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 8)
  - Reports-Clay County, Kentucky, 1956-1962; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"Colorado, a Study of Educational Finance", September 1968; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 10)
  - Reports-"Cuba, Missouri, A Study of Inadequate Board Policies and Damaging Personnel Practices", May 1968; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 11)
  - Reports-"Dekalb County, Georgia, A Profile of Paternalism in Public Education", July 1968; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 12)
  - Reports-"Delaware, A Study of School Finance: Failure to Adapt to Change", January 1968; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 13)
  - Reports-"Desegregation and the Rights of Educators" (Mississippi & Louisiana), September 1970; Series 2 (Box 994, Folder 14)
  - Reports-"Detroit, A Study of Barriers to Equal Educational Opportunity in a Large City", March 1967; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 1)
  - Reports-"Developing Personnel Policies", 1963; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 2)
  - Reports-"Dismissal of Teachers Because of Membership in Local Association", 1922; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"The Elgin Report", 1922; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 4)
  - Report of an Evaluation - Portland, Oregon: An Analysis of Current Education Conditions in the Portland School System, November 1967; series 2 (Box 4290, Folder 23)
  - Reports-"Fair Dismissal Procedures for a School System", 1960-1966; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"Fair Dismissal Standards", February 1969; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 6)
  - Reports-"Financial Support of the Public Schools of South Dakota", August 1967; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"Florida, a Study of Political Atmosphere as it Affects Public Education", March 1966; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 8)
  - Reports-"Florida, a Study of Political Atmosphere as it Affects Public Schools", March 1966; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"Florida, a Study of Political Atmosphere as it Affects Public Schools", March 1966; Series 2 (Box 996, Folder 10)
  - Reports-"Fort Wayne, Indiana, When the Policy-Making and Administrative Bodies Fail to Recognize and Utilize the Professional Talents of the Instructional Staff", April 1967; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 1)
  - Reports-"Freedom to Teach, Freedom to Learn", 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 2)
  - Reports-"Grievance Administration", May 1971; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"The Grievance Representative", December 1971; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 4)
  - Reports-"Guidelines for Professional Sanctions", 1963-1966; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"Guidelines for Professional Sanctions", November 1963; Series 2 (Box 1520, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"Guidelines for Retention of Staff for School Districts Moving from Dual to Unified System", 1966; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 6)
  - Reports-"Hyde County, North Carolina, School Boycott and the Roots of Conflict", September 1969; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"Inconsistent School Governance: Personnel Practices in Disarray", October 1972; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 8)
  - Reports-Index, 1972-1975; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"Indianapolis, Indiana" (Synopsis), May 1960; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 10)
  - Report of an Investigation: Belleville, New Jersey: A Study of Professional Responsibility when a Superintendent has Tenure of Office, January 1966; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 1)
  - Report of an Investigation:Colorado: A Study of Educational Finance, September 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 2)
  - Report of an Investigation: Cuba, Missouri: A Study of Inadequate Board Policies and Damaging Personnel Practices, May 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 3)
  - Report of an Investigation: Dekalb County, Georgia: A Profile of Paternalism in Public Education, July 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 4)
  - Report of an Investigation: Hyde County, North Carolina: School Boycott and the Roots of the Conflict, September 1969; series 17 (Box 4291, Folder 5)
  - Report of an Investigation: Kentucky, Education in kentucky: A Legacy of Unkept Promise, May 1971; series 17 (Box 4291, Folder 6)
  - Report of an Investigation: Minneapolis, Minnesota: A School System with a period of Grace, March 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 7)
  - Report of an Investigation: New Hampshire: A State of Neglected Opportunity, April 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 8)
  - Report of an Investigation: New Haven, Connecticut: A Case of Unintentional Neglect, August 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 9)
  - Report of an Investigation: Oakland, California: A Community in Transition with a School System Too Slowly Adapting, May 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 10)
  - Report of an Investigation: Pulaski County Special School District, Arkansas: A School Board Chronically Divided: A Study in Irresponsibility, November 1969; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 11)
  - Reports-"Investigation Reports Abridgments" (Vols. 1 & 2), 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 11)
  - Report of an Investigation: Sewanhaka, New York: Where Sectionalism within a School District Deters Educationall Progress, December 1967; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 12)
  - Report of an Investigation:South Dakota: A Statewide Study of Public School Finance and Conditions in the Schools, October 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 13)
  - Reports-"An Irrational Tax Structure: An Imperiled School System", October 1971; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 12)
  - Reports-"Kanawha County, West Virginia, A Textbook Study in Cultural Conflict", February 1975; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 13)
  - Reports-"Kansas, A Statewide Study of Educational Conditions and Financial Support", November 1967; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 14)
  - Reports-"Kansas, A Statewide Study of Educational Conditions and Financial Support", January 1968; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 15)
  - Reports-"Kentucky, Education in Kentucky: A Legacy of Unkept Promise", May 1971; Series 2 (Box 997, Folder 16)
  - Reports-"Knoxville, Tennessee, When a City Government Fails to Give Full Support to its Schools", March 1967; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 1)
  - Reports-"Levittown, New York" (Synopsis), January 1962; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 2)
  - Reports-"The Local Education Association and Grievance Adjustment", 1966-1969; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"Material for Use at Conferences Dealing with the Drafting of a Teacher Tenure Act", May 1971; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 4)
  - Reports-"Menominee Sanctions Investigation", September 1967; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"Minneapolis, Minnesota, A School System with a Period of Grace", March 1968; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 6)
  - Reports-"NEA Commission on Professional Rights and Responsibilities", 1963-1972; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"National Society of Professors", circa 1963; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 8)
  - Reports-"New Hampshire, A State of Neglected Opportunity", April 1968; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"New Haven, Connecticut, A Case of Unintentional Neglect", August 1968; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 10)
  - Reports-"Oakland, California, A Community in Transition with a School Sytem too Slowly Adapting", May 1968; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 11)
  - Reports-"Oklahoma", February 1965; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 12)
  - Reports-"Oklahoma" (Synopsis), June 1965; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 13)
  - Reports-"Oklahoma, A Revaluation of Conditions Detrimental to an Effective Public Educational Program", March 1968; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 14)
  - Reports-"Portland, Oregon, An Analysis of Current Education Conditions in the Portland School System", November 1967; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 15)
  - Reports-"Practical Personnel Policies Essential for Good Schools", 1966; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 16)
  - Reports-"A Preliminary Inquiry of Dekalb County", October 1967; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 17)
  - Reports-"Professional Practices Regulations", April 1965; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 18)
  - Reports-"Professional Rights and Responsibilities Handbook", 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 19)
  - Reports-"Professional Rights and Responsibilities and the Local Education Association", 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 20)
  - Reports-"Professional Rights and Responsibilities and the Local Education Association of Television Teachers", 1963; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 21)
  - Report of a Public School Study; kansas: A Statewide Study of Educational Conditions and Financial Support, January 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 14)
  - Reports-"Pulaski County, Special School District, Arkansas, A School Board Chronically Divided: A Study in Irresponsibility", November 1969; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 22)
  - Reports-"Report of Task Force Appointed to Study the Problem of Displaced School Personnel Related to School Desegregation and the Employment Status of Recently Prepared Negro College Graduates Certified to Teach in Seventeen States", December 1965; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 23)
  - Report of a Revaluation: Oklahoma: A Revaluation of Conditions Detrimental to an Effective Public Education Program, March 1968; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 15)
  - Reports-"Rights and Liabilities of Teacher Associations in the Imposition of Sanctions", May 1962; Series 2 (Box 998, Folder 24)
  - Reports-"Rules of Procedure for Investigations", 1969; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 1)
  - Reports-"Santa Fe, New Mexico" (Synopsis), January 1961; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 2)
  - Reports-"School Finance in Arizona: A State-Local Partnership", January 1970; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"Sewanhaka, New York, Where Sectionalism within a School District Deters Educational Progrees", December 1967; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 4)
  - Report of the Sixteenth Annual Conference on the Critics and the Schools "Extremism on the American Scene", 1965; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 16)
  - Reports-"Some Facts on NEA PR&R Commission Investigations", 1963; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"South Dakota, A Statewide Study of Public School Finance and Conditions in the Schools", October 1968; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 6)
  - Reports-"Southern University, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, A Study of Student Protest-Suggestions for University Response", September 1973; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"Standards for the Conduct of Investigations", May 1969; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 8)
  - Reports-"Sub-Committee on Human Rights of Educators", 1966; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"Suggestions for Defense Against Extremist Attack: Sex Education in the Public Schools", March 1970; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 10)
  - Reports-"Taking the Grief Out of Grievances in Public School Systems", 1958-1967; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 11)
  - Report of Task Force Survey of Teacher Displacement in Seventeen States, December 1965; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 17)
  - Reports-"TEPS and PR&R", May 1964; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 12)
  - Reports-"Tenure-What and Why", 1961-1963; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 13)
  - Reports-"When Employers Interfere with Association Activity", November 1971; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 14)
  - Rules of Procedure for Investigation, ca. 1969; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook (Postcards), 1963-1966; Series 2 (Box 995, Oversize 1)
  - Seminar-"How Grievance Processing Affects Associations and School Systems", February 1970; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 15)
  - Seminar-Professional Negotiation (Stanford & Chicago), 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 1520, Folder 4)
  - A Special Study: School Finance in Arizona: A State-Local Partnership, January 1970; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 19)
  - A Special Study in Washington: An Irrational Tax Structure: An Imperiled School System, October 1971; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 20)
  - Speeches and Articles [file 1/2], 1951-1968; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 16)
  - Speeches and Articles [file 2/2], 1951-1968; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 17)
  - Standards for the Conduct of Investigations: A Report of a National Seminar, May 1969; series 2 (Box 4291, Folder 21)
  - Statements, 1966-1969; series 2 (Box 4312, Folder 8)
  - Statements of Policy, 1955-1956; series 2 (Box 4312, Folder 9)
  - Studying Teacher Classroom Behavior to Determine How Paraprofessionals Can Help in the Classroom, May 1969; series 2 (Box 4312, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Committee on Human Rights of Educators, circa 1965; series 2 (Box 4292, Folder 1)
  - Suggestions for Defense Against Extremist Attack: Sex Education in the Public Schools, March 1970; series 2 (Box 4292, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Career Fact Books, 1962-1966; Series 2 (Box 4048, Folder 10)
  - Understanding Intergroup Relations, 1972; Series 2 (Box 1000, Oversize 1)
  - When Employers interfere with Association Activity, November 1971; series 2 (Box 4292, Folder 3)
  - The Workshop Newsletter, June 1964-June 1968; Series 2 (Box 999, Folder 18)
  - Workshop on PR&R (First), June 1962; Series 2 (Box 1001, Folder 1)
  - Workshop on PR&R (Second), June 1963; Series 2 (Box 1001, Folder 2)
  - Workshop on PR&R (Third), June 1964; Series 2 (Box 1001, Folder 3)
  - Workshop on PR&R (Fourth), June 1966; Series 2 (Box 1001, Folder 4)
  - Workshop on PR&R-Materials [file 1/2], 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 1001, Folder 5)